http://www.johnstonesupply.com/storefront/privacyStatement.ep

Johnstone Supply | Wholesale Distributor to the HVAC, Refrigeration and Property Maintenance Industries
Belts
Blower Assembly (Without Motor)
Supplies
Air Distribution (Grilles, Sheet Metal, etc.)
Ventilation& IAQ
Indoor Air Quality (IAQ)
Johnstone Privacy Statement
Johnstone Supply, Inc. is committed to respecting your privacy. We recognize the need to respect your personally identifiable information that you share with Johnstone. Personally identifiable information is any information that is associated with your name. Johnstone uses your information to assist us in our goal of providing world-class customer service. To help us continue to provide a quality web site and a rich navigational experience, we may track your use of our Web Site.
We are publishing this Online Privacy statement to make you aware of our Privacy Policy in case you choose to share your personally identifiable information.
Currently, Johnstone Supply, Inc. may use your personally identifiable information in the following ways (but may not be limited to):
Shared with the appropriate Johnstone store
Shared with business partners who also have a Privacy Policy
Shared with the Human Resources department if you are responding to an online employment opportunity
Direct marketing by our stores or by Johnstone Supply, Inc. approved vendors
Credit card numbers are only used for processing payments and will not be used for other purposes
Johnstone Supply, Inc. supports industry self-regulation efforts on privacy by working with such organizations as the Online Privacy Alliance and the Better Business Bureau Online. We also work with other business organizations who are working to protect consumer privacy. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please email the Johnstone Webmaster.
Johnstone Info
About Johnstone Supply
Sales Policy
Press Releases
SDS
Mobile Site
Contractor Resources
Tax Credits
Credit Application (Fillable PDF)
Your Request is Processing ...
Your session is about to expire, would you like to continue?
Johnstone Supply. All rights reserved.
This site is optimized for IE7 or later, Firefox, Chrome and Safari
